ideaswatch.com 2011-05-26

# IdeasWatch: Privacy policy

[Maintop Businesses s.r.o.](http://www.maintop.biz/en) is the creator and publisher of the web pages available at IdeasWatch.com, and all linked pages, features, content, or applications (collectively, the "Site"). 

##  Extent of Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy covers Maintop Businesses s.r.o.’s treatment of personal information that we collect when you are on the Site. This policy covers our treatment of any personal information that our business partners share with us. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Maintop Businesses s.r.o. does not own or control, including but not limited to third party services you access through Maintop Businesses s.r.o., or to individuals that we do not employ or manage. We collect the following types of information from our users:

##  Information Collected From Registered Visitors By Our Server

During the sign up we collect information necessary to provide the promised functions of IdeasWatch:

###  Email address

We send out emails regarding the status of your ideas or ideas you are watching. Besides that we may also send Informative emails about IdeasWatch website in general such as announcement of new functions or changes to the Site. If you want to unsubscribe from the Informative emails, just send an email to [unsubscribe@ideaswatch.com](mailto:unsubscribe@ideaswatch.com). 

**We do not share your email address with any third party.**

###  Name/Nickname

Your name or nickname is publicly available via  Inspirers Chart along with statistics of your ideas.

##  Information Collected from Facebook

We collect only aggregate information about popularity of ideas on Facebook. 

**At any point we do not associate this data with particular visitors of the Site.**

##  Information Collected From All Visitors By Our Server 

Whenever you interact with the IdeasWatch website, we may receive and store certain types of information. This information includes the data stored by the server in server logs, such as your IP address, IdeasWatch cookie information, and the information you request from the server. Maintop Businesses s.r.o. may use this information to detect problems with the server, make changes so that the site is easier to use or create statistics. Maintop Businesses s.r.o. may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. 

##  Information Collected From All Visitors via Google Analytics

If you visit this site and you have javascript enabled, your actions are tracked by Google Analytics. These Google services collect the following types of information: 

  * Type of user agent (web browser) used, software manufacture and version number. 
  * Type of operating system 
  * Screen colors (color processing ability of the users screen) 
  * Javascript support 
  * Flash version 
  * Screen resolution 
  * Network location and IP address Can include country, city, state, region, county, or any other geographic data. 
  * Hostname 
  * Bandwidth (internet connection speed) 
  * Time of visit 
  * Pages visited 
  * Time spent on each page of the website 
  * Referring site statistics 
  * The website (URI) the user came through in order to arrive at this website (example: clicking on a hyperlink from Yahoo.com that took the user to this website) 
  * Search engine query used (example: typing in a phrase into a search engine like Google, and clicking on a link from that search engine) 

This data is primarily used to optimize our website for our visitors. It's important to note that this data **DOES NOT** include any personalized identification information such as: 

  * Names 
  * Phone Numbers 
  * Email Addresses 
  * Mailing Addresses 
  * Social Security Numbers 
  * Bank Account Numbers 
  * Credit Card Information 

## Cookies

Cookies are simple pieces of information that we store on your hard drive through your Web browser. These cookies do not collect personal information.
